FRANKLINE KIPLANGAT

P.O. BOX 507-20210, LITEIN, KENYA. (+254)724375662

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/frankline-kiplangat

Email: kipfrankline@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://portfolio-frank.herokuapp.com/ **GitHub:** https://github.com/Frankline-Kiplangat

Nationality: Kenyan Gender: Male

Languages: English & Kiswahili (fluent)

Date of Birth: 29th June 1996 ID Number: 32849179

Personal Brand

I seek a company where I can use my experience and education to help the company meet and surpass its goals. I want to be part of a challenging team which strives for the better growth of the organization and which explores my potential and provide me with the opportunity to enhance my talent with an aim of being an asset to an organization.

Programming Skills

Strong: HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Python (Django & Flask), jQuery, PostgreSQL.

Experienced: Angular, JavaScript.

Personal Skills

- High performance computing.
- Strong organizational skills and attention to details.
- Strong communication skills, works well with teams and under minimal supervision.
- Digital and Content Marketing Skills.

Employment History

Data Clerk - Cloud Factory Kenya

Sept 2020 - Sept 2022

Duties and responsibilities.

• Reviewing and entering data into databases quickly and accurately.

Sales Representative- Safaricom Home Fibre

January – March 2020

Duties and Responsibilities.

- Promoting and Selling Safaricom Home Fibre products.
- Ensure optical customer experience through service given and follow up on all inquiries.

Network Operator- Jumia Kenya

June 2019 – December 2019

Duties and Responsibilities.

- Recording new stock as it comes in.
- Shipping products using Warehouse Management System; Preparing and completing orders for delivery according to schedule.

Intern - ESRI Eastern Africa

June 2017 – Aug 2017

Duties and Responsibilities.

- Creating maps and graphs, using Geographic Information System (GIS) software and data collection equipment.
- Analyzing and modelling relationships between geographic datasets.

Education

Moringa School

April - September 2020

Certificate in Software Development - Full Stack.

University of Nairobi

September 2014 - December 2018

Bachelor of Science in Astronomy & Astrophysics.

• Second Class Degree, Lower Division.

Relevant Courses

- Theoretical and Mathematical physics.
- Remote Sensing.
- Astronautics.

Light Touch Computer College

Aug 2014

Computer Packages.

Kabianga Boys High School

2010-2013

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education (B+).

Interests & Hobbies

Networking, travelling, swimming and doing community work.

References

1. Caroline Muthoni Team Captain- Cloud Factory Kenya Peponi Road, Nairobi, Kenya. Mobile: 0713906417

Email: caroline.muthoni@es.cloudfactory.com

2. Ian Mutuku

Team Leader - Finley International Ltd

P.O. BOX 30847-00100,

Nairobi, Kenya. Mobile: 0720305828

Email: iansilamutuku.is@gmail.com

3. James Ndichu

Installation Technician - Safaricom Home Fibre

P.O BOX 30197-00100,

Nairobi Kenya.

Mobile: 0721755881

Email: jamesndichu127@gmail.com